Pouya Mohseni (He/Him/His)

Email: mohseni0pouyai@gmail.com Mobile: +98 (933) 794-0620

Summary

Being a dedicated student of Computer Science with a passion for Deep Learning, I've actively engaged in research projects, teaching roles, and extracurricular activities to foster a versatile skill set. Beyond academic expertise, I've developed soft skills, such as project management, collaborative teamwork, and effective communication.

EDUCATION

University of Tehran

Tehran, Iran

Sep 2019 - Present

Bachelor of Computer Science

o GPA: 18.28/20 (Overall: 3.84, Last two years: 4/4)

Minor in Entrepreneurship

o GPA 19.39/20 (Overall: 4/4)

Publications

• Mohseni, Pouya, Hedieh Sajedi, and Khalid Hussain. "Gift Recommendation Systems: [Accepted for Publication] A Review.", Electronic Commerce Research.

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

University of Tehran

Tehran, Iran

Supervised by Dr. Bagher BabaAli

Oct 2023 - Present

- Languages & Softwares: Python, Toarch, LATEX, Git
- Work Results: Conducted research on self-supervised methods utilized in speech and music processing. Progressing towards pretraining a model on Eastern music and developing a music information retrieval on downstream tasks.

University of Tehran

Tehran, Iran

Research Assistant – Supervised by Dr. Hedieh Sajedi

Dec 2022 - Aug 2023

- Languages & Softwares: Python, LATEX, Git
- Work Results: Conducted research on recommendation systems with a specific focus on e-commerce. Authored a review paper on gift recommendation systems. Additionally, introduced a novel recommendation system leveraging Twitter's user data to emphasize personality traits.

The PDAT laboratory at Toosi University of Technology

Tehran, Iran

Part-time Researcher

Aug 2022 - Dec 2022

- Languages & Softwares: Python, Django, Docker, LATEX, Git
- Work Results: Engaged in research in the intersection of quantum computing and machine learning algorithms. Developed and implemented a quantum neural network algorithm to be trained on astronomical data.

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

University of Tehran

Tehran, Iran

Teaching Assistant, Advanced Information Retrieval

Sep 2023 - Present

University of Tehran

Tehran, Iran

Teaching Assistant, Discrete Mathematics

Dec 2022 - Jun 2023

Work Experience

Borhan Credit Rating

Tehran, Iran

Part-time Junior Data Analyst

Mar 2021 - Dec 2022

- o Learned Software & Frameworks: Python, Pandas, Flask, Docker, Excel, Git, REST API
- Work Results: Developed a program that rates investment funds according to the company's methodology, eliminating the requirement for two specialized personnel.

SKILLS

• Programming Languages: Python, C++, Assembly, R

• Frameworks & Tools: Scikit-learn, Keras\TensorFlow, Pandas, Git, Flask

• Typescript Languages: LATEX, HTML

LANGUAGES

• Farsi: Native Speaker • English (TOEFL): 109 (R: 30, L: 30, S: 25, W: 24) - Test Date: October 14, 2023